Guide to the Max J. and Ruth Clement Bond Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Country, Regional and Subject Files, 1935-1995
  - Subseries II.2: Subject Files, 1935-1995
    - Library of Congress, 1980 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Lincoln University, 1985-1994 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Kentucky Opera Association--Complaint, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Parker, Judge Barrington, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Programs and Events, 1949-1988, Undated (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Refugees, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Robinson, Henry S., 1960-1988, Undated (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Sociology, Department of--University of Southern California, 1959-1966 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Sociology, Negro Doctorates in--Questionnaires, Undated (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Southern Negro Youth Conference, 1940, Undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Tennessee Valley Association (TVA)
      - "Effects of Pickwick Landing Reservoir on Waterloo and Riverton, Alabama," 1935 (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Negro Training Program, 1935, Undated (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Quilts--Exhibit, 1990-1995 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Textile Museum, 1988-1992 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Tuskegee Institute--Army Airforce Training Program, 1944, Undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Tuskegee Institute--Ephemera, 1942-1943, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - United States Civil Rights, 1963-1970 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Women--Reports, 1977, 1991, Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Washington, D. C.
      - General, 1968-1986, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Education, 1950s-1960s (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Park Bill--Max Bond Senate Testimony, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Program for Laymen Overseas, 1966, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Series III: Writings, 1930-1988
  Manuscript drafts and notes by J. Max Bond make up the bulk of this series. Subject matter, largely concerning civil rights, the Black Panthers, and the Nixon administration, dates most of the manuscripts to the late 1960s-1970s. Where possible, drafts of the same manuscript have been grouped together and organized alphabetically, using the original titles; however, lack of dates makes it impossible to ascertain the chronological order of the drafts. A small amount of material in this series is by Ruth Bond and included here is her Master's thesis. The material is arranged alphabetically.
  Note: Most reports written by J. Max Bond, Sr. and Ruth Clement Bond can be found in Subseries II.1: Country and Regional, 1939-1990.
  - J. Max Bond, Sr.
    - "Aging"--Drafts and Notes, 1975, 1980, Undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - "For America's Senior Citizens--Departure or Security," 1971-1972, Undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - “American Myth”--Drafts, Undated, (5 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 12 to 16)
    - “Becoming a Negro” --Fragment, Undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - "Bicentennial--Chapter 1", Undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - "Education of the Negro in America"--Notes, Undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - "Golden Thread", Undated (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 20 to 21)
    - "Holocaust Makers and Dream Killers", Undated (2 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 22 to 23)
    - "Martin Luther King Assassination", Undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - "The Modern American Termites", Undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Minorities and Desegregation--Drafts and Research Material, 1970s (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Movements, Undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - "Nation Out of Focus"--Outline and Proposal, 1974, Undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - [Nation Out of Focus], Undated (5 Folders) (Box 19, Folder 29 to 33)
    - [Nation Out of Focus], Undated (6 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 1 to 6)
    - "New Nation", Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - "The Pall of Mylai", Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - "Panthers"--Draft, Undated (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 9 to 10)
    - "Permissiveness", Undated (6 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 11 to 16)
    - "Religion", Undated (3 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 17 to 19)
    - "Sickness", (3 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 20 to 22)
    - "Southern Strategy", Circa 1970s (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - "Teachers of Democracy", Undated (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - "Youth"--Draft, Undated (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - "Washington's Elderly World," Circa 1970s (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Untitled Drafts, Undated (2 Folders) (Box 20, Folder 27 to 28)
    - Untitled Drafts, Undated (5 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 1 to 5)
    - Untitled Drafts--Ruth's Edits, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Untitled Drafts and Notes, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Ruth Bond
    - “Birth of an Article,” 1988 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - “Birth of an Article”--Notes and Drafts, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - “Citizens of Christ and Democracy,” Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - “The Criminal in English Drama"--M.A. Thesis 1930 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - “The Criminal in English Drama"--M.A. Thesis --Notes, Circa 1930 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - "Trivia: Inauguration Day," 1969 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Untitled Drafts, 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Notes and Drafts, Undated, (2 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 15 to 16)
- Series IV: Organizations, 1942-1995
  Newsletters, correspondence, notes, minutes, and photographs, related to the many organizations to which the Bonds belonged, make up the bulk of this, the largest series in the collection. The material comprising this series was scattered throughout the holdings with no discernable order. Documents, therefore, were gathered from across the collection and arranged chronologically by decade and, where appropriate, by years. At times, documents from different organizations were found nested together. Generally these stray documents have been left where they were found; for example, the Association of American Foreign Service Women (AAFSW) folders also contain material related to the Africa-America Institute (AAI) and other organizations. These cases reflect the very strong ties, both in terms of shared personnel and subject matter, between the organizations to which the Bonds belonged. In addition, the Bonds frequently received a very small amount of literature—often only a single document—from a vast array of organizations. The material related to these organizations has been grouped together within the General Organizations folders and arranged chronologically. Within the General Organizations folders there is much material dedicated to Women’s groups.
  The Boys and Girls Club of Greater Washington (BGCGW: also known as Eastern Branch Boys' Club of Greater Washington) and its affiliate, the Women's Auxiliary Board (WAB), in which Max and Ruth Bond held leadership roles respectively, represent the single largest organizations within the series. Reflecting their organizational structure, the material relating to both groups has been kept together. The WAB’s President's Book contains a representative assortment of documents related to this organization between 1970 and 1975, including a history, minutes, photograph albums, and materials regarding receptions for other organizations—especially those organizations associated with the Bonds.
  The Association of American Foreign Service Women (AAFSW) was strongly involved in the BGCGW/WAB. Although the AAFSW and WAB were two distinct organizations, many AAFSW members came to occupy leading roles in the WABGC. The AAFSW—and, through it, BGCGW/WAB— was also affiliated with the National Council of Women of the United States (NCWUS); Ruth Bond held a number of roles within each organization and the materials here reflect that involvement.
  Also within this series is material regarding the Africa-America Institute (AAI) and its African Scholarship Program of American Universities (ASPAU). The primary aim of the AAI was to facilitate the education and training of Africans studying in the United States by providing both financial support in the form of scholarships and a social, cultural, and legal support network. During the 1960s and early 1970s—the period of the Max and Ruth Bond's greatest involvement in the organization—the ASPAU was responsible for the selection, placement, funding, training, and orientation of students; Max and Ruth Bond were active in the selection and placement of scholarship students.
  Material regarding the African-American Scholars Council (AASC) can be found within the AAI material. Although the two organizations were not officially aligned, the AASC was founded by James L. Hope, who had previously run the AAI’s scholarship program. Also within the AAI documents are materials relating to the Hospitality and Information Service (THIS) for Diplomatic Residents and Families, as well as the Student Counseling Service and its subsidiary organizations, including the African-American Women's Council.
  Of general note, the Washington Women's Council is the successor of African-American Wives Group. It is through Church Women United that Ruth Bond became involved with the Bicentennial celebrations of 1976.
  - General, 1942, 1954 1960s-1994, (5 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 17 to 21)
  - General--Women, 1950s-1994, Undated (3 Folders) (Box 21, Folder 22 to 24)
  - General--Women, 1950s-1994, Undated (7 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 1 to 7)
  - African Women's Organization in America, 1965-1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - African-American Institute (AAI)
    - General, 1963-1981 (6 Folders) (Box 22, Folder 9 to 14)
    - General, 1982-1990s, (3 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 1 to 3)
    - African-American Scholars Council, 1974-1975 (with "Women of Africa") (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - African-American Women's Council, 1967-1972 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - African Embassies, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - The African Student in Washington--Transcripts, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - The African Student in Washington--Voice of America--AudioTapes 1-3, 1976 (Box 42)
    - Student Aid Documents, 1971-1983 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Student Aid Documents--National Association for Foreign Student Affairs, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Student's Ball--An African Evening, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - THIS--The Hospitality and Information Service, 1966-1969 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Washington Women's Council, 1961-1968 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - African-American Women's Association
    - General, 1971-1976, (6 Folders) (Box 23, Folder 13 to 18)
    - General, 1976-1990s, Undated, (10 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 1 to 11)
    - Photograph Album--Beige, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Photograph Album--Black, Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Africare, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - American Foreign Service Association, 1970-1971, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - American Red Cross, 1985-1988 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Amicale Americano-Malagasy, 1984-1985 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Association of American Foreign Service Women
    - General, 1967-1969 (2 Folders) (Box 24, Folder 16 to 17)
    - General, 1970-1990s, (8 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 1 to 8)
  - Black Women's Agenda, 1979, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Boys & Girls Club of Greater Washington
    - General, 1968-1975, Undated, (6 Folders) (Box 25, Folder 10 to 15)
    - General, 1976-1995, Undated, (8 Folders) (Box 26, Folder 1 to 8)
    - Annual National Conference, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Award Presented to J. Max Bond, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Board Meetings and General Documents, 1975-1983 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - "Boy's Club," 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - "Boys' & Girls' Club," 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - "Forms & Letters, Treasurers Reports, Grants," 1986-1987 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - History--Women's Auxiliary Board, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Photographs
      - General, 1970-1971, 1986, 1989, Undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Bound Album, 1970-1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - President's Book Women's Auxiliary Board, 1970-1975 (Bound) (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Recipes, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Talent Show Journal, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Treasurer Reports and Minutes, 1970-1983 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - "Women's Auxiliary Education Assistance," 1986-1987 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Capital Hill Restoration Society, 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Church Women United (CWU)
    - General, 1960s-1975 (13 Folders) (Box 27, Folder 4 to 16)
    - General, 1975-1990s, Undated (6 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 1 to 6)
    - Anniversary, 30th--Celebration, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Anti-War Material, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Bethune, Mary McLeod--Funeral & Memorial, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Bicentennial, 1975 (2 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 10 to 11)
    - Board of Managers Program, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Conference of Church and Synagogue Women, 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Conference, Governor Romney's, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - International Women’s Year, 1975-1977 (3 Folders) (Box 28, Folder 15 to 17)
    - International Women’s Year--Report--"...To Form a More Perfect Union...," 1976 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - People’s Platform, 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Planetary Pupil, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - World Day of Prayer, 1974-1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Civil Rights--Leadership Conference, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Committee for National Security, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Black Caucus, 1970-1971 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Diplomatic and Consular Officers, Retired (Dacor), 1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - District of Columbia Bicentennial, 1987-1989 (3 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 8 to 10)
  - Foreign Student Service Council, 1967-1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Friends of the National Museum of African Art, 1985-1988 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Inter-American Commission of Women, 1972-1980 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - International Visitors Service, 1967-1969 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Liberian Ore Limited, 1963-1992, (3 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 15 to 17)
  - National Association for Community Development, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - National Council of Churches (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - National Council of Negro Women
    - 1969-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 29, Folder 20 to 21)
    - "International Women's United for Equality," 1975 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - "Report and Recommendations: Feasibility Trip to Senegal, Ivory Coast and Togo," 1978 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - "Women & Housing: A Report on Sex Discrimination in Five American Cities," 1975 (Box 30, Folder 2 to 3)
  - National Council of Women of the United States, 1964-1976, Undated, (7 Folders) (Folder 4 to 10)
    - "85th Annual Meeting," 1973 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Civil Rights for Women of Conscience, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - White House Conference "To Fulfill These Rights," 1966 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Northwestern University, 1985-1992 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Overseas Education Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Public Television--Community Service Awards, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Rural America--Coming of Age, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - United Planning Organization, "The Polycultural Pre-School Program," 1975 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - United Nations
    - General, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Decade for Women, 1984-1986 (3 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 3 to 5)
    - UNIFEM, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - International Women’s Year 1973-1977 (6 Folders) (Box 31, Folder 7 to 12)
    - International Women's Year--French Materials, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Universities--General, 1970s-1990s (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Youth for Understanding, 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Widening Horizons, 1964-1975, Undated, (3 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Women & Labor, 1973-1989 (2 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 4 to 5)
  - Women's International Religious Fellowship, 1970-1972 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Women's National Democratic Club, 1968-1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - World Council of Churches, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - World Day of Prayer, 1958-1988, (2 Folders) (Box 32, Folder 9 to 10)
- Series V: Personal, 1914-1995
  Family memorabilia, awards and travel ephemera; biographical manuscripts, interviews and notes concerning the Clement-Bond family history; drafts of the Bond children's school papers and documents relating to individual interests; diaries, day books, and journals; and financial files, all of which capture the personal lives of the Bond family, are found here.
  - Subseries V.1: General, Circa 1914-1992
    The materials in this subseries range across decades and include awards, diplomas, birth certificates, educational and employment documents, clippings, and extended family genealogical and biographical materials, as well as ephemera.
    - Biographical and Family History
      - Article--"The Life and Times of J. Max Bond," by Ruth M. Bond, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Biographical Notes, Undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Bond, James--"Life on the Margins: An Autobiography," Undated (2 Folders) Needs to be Photocopied. (Box 32, Folder 12 to 13)
      - Bond, James--Tributes, 1979-2003 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Bond, Ruth--Oral History Transcripts, 1992-1994 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Clement-Bond Family History, Circa 1946 1970s (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Clement, Emma C. 1914, 1946, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Clippings, 1950s-1992 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Awards, 1975-1991 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Bond Children--Physician Reports, 1942 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      [Restricted until 2032]
    - George Bond, Circa 1950s (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - George Bond--Diploma--London School of Economics, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Jane Bond
      - Bibliographies and Notes, 1967-1980, Undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Curriculum Vitae, Undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Economics and International Politics--Articles by Others, 1970s-1980s (3 Folders) (Box 33, Folder 7 to 9)
      - And Fernando Howard, 1953-1963, Undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Journals, 1972, Undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Sarah Lawrence College, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - "Le Syndicalisme Minoritaire..." and Notes, 1989, Undated (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Washington High School, 1948 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Max Bond, Jr.
      - Architecture, 1968-1980 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Financial, 1949, 1953-1958 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - School Papers, 1951-1952 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - J. Max Bond, Sr
      - Curriculum Vitae, 1967, Undated (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Employment--Applications and Reports, Circa 1960-1967 (Box 33, Folder 19)
      - Employment--Letters of Recommendation, 1967 (Box 33, Folder 20)
      - Employment--Travel Documents and Vouchers (Box 33, Folder 21)
      - Death and Funeral, 1981-1982, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - J. Max Bond, Sr. and Ruth Clement Bond--Wills, 1981-1991 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Ruth Clement Bond
      - Class Notes, 1927 (Box 33, Folder 24)
      - Bibliographies, 1920 Circa 1950s (Box 33, Folder 25)
      - Employment Reviews, 1982-1983 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Sketches, Circa 1950s and 1960s (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Travel Ephemera, Circa 1950s-1960s (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Ephemera
      - Audio Tape--Unidentified, Undated (Box 42)
      - Award--Liberia, 1953 (Rolled) (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Awards, 1957-1983 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Diploma, 1925 (Rolled) (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Haiti Stamps, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Boy's Club Award, 1978, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Equal Rights Amendment Sash, Undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Eyeglasses, Undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Lincoln University Paper Weight, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Pins--Adlai Stevenson, Undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Wallet, Undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Subseries V.2. Daybooks, Diaries, Notebooks and Personal Documents, 1925-1995
    The bulk of this series is made up of diaries, notebooks and agendas kept by Ruth Clement Bond. Ruth's agendas—her daily appointment books—include appointments, invitations and often phone calls—both personal and professional—and mark her many and varied cultural interests and the extent of her activity with the organizations with which she worked.
    Many of the agendas also include messages, lists of addresses, notes for meetings, notes on various readings or topics of interest to her, and sometimes inserted note cards or invitations. Her notebooks, similarly, include addresses, lists of expenses, and notes on readings or meetings. The diaries and travel journals, while rarely kept on a daily basis, do include many lengthy entries regarding living and traveling abroad.
    There are a few notebooks kept by J. Max Bond, Sr. in this series, and both Ruth and Max maintained diaries in 1956, the year that Max was appointed as Education Advisor to Afghanistan’s Minister of Education.
    Also here are guest books, baby books, passports, driver's licenses and other personal documents.
    - Bond, Max Sr.
      - Automobile Documents, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Diary--Afghanistan, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Diary and Notebook, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Driver's License--Nyasaland, 1962 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Guest Book, Undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Notebook, circa 1960s (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Notebook--Changing Cultural Image in the Black World, Undated (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Notebook--USC, circa 1930s (2 Notebooks) (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Passports, 1944-1989 (4) (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Personal Documents, 1960s-1970s (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - Scrapbook--Newspaper Clippings, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Bond, Ruth Clement
      - Agendas or Day Books, 1959, 1968-1995 (19) (Box 35, Folder 1 to 19)
      - Calendars, 1987-1991 (3) (Box 35, Folder 20 to 22)
      - Diaries and Journals
        - Diary, 1933 (Box 36, Folder 1)
        - Diary, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 2)
        - Diary, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 3)
        - Diary, 1992, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 4)
        - Diary--Afghanistan and Travel, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 5)
        - Diary--Malawi, 1964-1965 (Box 36, Folder 6)
        - Diary--Journal, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 7)
        - Journal--London, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Notebooks
        - General, 1958, 1973-1992, Undated (10) (Box 35, Folder 23 to 32)
        - Africa, Undated (Box 35, Folder 33)
        - Africa--Liberia, 1954 (Box 35, Folder 34)
        - Expenses, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 9)
        - Expenses--Trip to West Africa, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
        - Expenses and Travel, 1950-1963 (Box 36, Folder 11)
        - Organizations--General, 1972-1988 (6) (Box 36, Folder 12 to 17)
        - Organizations--African American Institute, 1963-1964, Undated (Box 36, Folder 18)
        - Organizations-- Association of American Foreign Service Women and Boys Club, 1968-1991, (2 Folders) (Box 36, Folder 19 to 20)
      - Personal Documents and Ephemera
        - Address Books, circa 1950s, Undated (5) (Box 36, Folder 21 to 25)
        - Driver Licenses--Africa, 1957, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 26)
        - French Phrase Book, 1954 (Box 36, Folder 27)
        - Guest Books, 1993 (2) (Box 36, Folder 28 to 29)
        - Graduation Bulletin--Northwestern University, 1925 (Box 36, Folder 30)
        - Passports, 1944-1972 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Bond, George Clement
      - Baby Book, 1936 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Driver’s License--International, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Bond, Max Jr.
      - Baby Book, 1935 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Subseries V.3: Financial, 1931-1994, Undated